export const questions = { 
	easy: [
		{
			question: "What is her favorite color?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Pink"
		},
		{
			question: "When is her birthday?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "June 13, 1996"
		},
		{
			question: "Name her cats.",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Dennis and Pablo"
		},
		{
			question: "Where did she go to college?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Cal State Fullerton"
		},
		{
			question: "How old is she?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "28"
		},
		{
			question: "What is her IG?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "funkyunicornn"
		},
		{
			question: "Sweet or savory?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Savory"
		},
		{
			question: "Outdoor or indoor?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Indoor"
		},
		{
			question: "Summer or winter?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Winter"
		},		
		{
			question: "Morning or night?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Night"
		},		
		{
			question: "In-person or online shopping",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "In-person"
		},
		{
			question: "Flats or drums?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Flats"
		},
		{
			question: "Comedy or drama?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Comedy"
		},
		{
			question: "What city does she live in?",
			difficulty: 1,
			answer: "Santa Ana"
		}
	],
	medium: [
		{
			question: "Favorite Sanrio character and why?",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "My Melody. She loves them all but chose one to stop herself from buying every character merch."
		},
		{
			question: "What was her previous job title?",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Social Media Manager"
		},
		{
			question: "What is her middle name?",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Hoa Nghiem"
		},
		{
			question: "Favorite anime",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Fruits Basket"
		},
		{
			question: "What did she study in college?",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Marketing"
		},
		{
			question: "What game did she clock over 1000 hours in?",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Animal Crossing: New Horizon"
		},
		{
			question: "Where did she last travel?",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Seattle"
		},
		{
			question: "What make and model of car does she drive?",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Toyota Yaris"
		},
		{
			question: "Favorite store",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Daiso"
		},
		{
			question: "Favorite fast food",
			difficulty: 2,
			answer: "Taco Bell"
		},
		
	],
	hard: [
		{
			question: "How many tattoos does she have?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "14"
		},
		{
			question: "If she were to get a third cat, what would their name be?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "Sawyer (the destroyer)"
		},
		{
			question: "What food does she hate the most?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "Cucumbers"
		},
		{
			question: "Favorite movie",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "Lego Batman/Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind"
		},
		{
			question: "What year did she start heleneshappyhobbies",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "2021"
		},
		{
			question: "When is her next pop-up market?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "Sat, June 29"
		},
		{
			question: "What shape is her tooth gem?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "Butterfly"
		},
		{
			question: "What is her webiste?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "heleneshappyhobbies.art"
		},
		{
			question: "How many smiskis does she have?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "24"
		},
		{
			question: "What is her In-n-out order?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "Plain cheeseburger, fries, and a diet soda"
		},
		{
			question: "When did Helene last travel to Vietnam?",
			difficulty: 3,
			answer: "Nov 2023"
		},
	]
}
